sup everyone cameras were u5p with a
very special video today now I know some
of you love my firm years so I
thought you know what it I'm gonna
do another one so here's my my
best buds
Superman and Sonic and batman we don't
need no suit on cuz he's like a
he's batman super
so anyways since I know how much you
love my foodies I thought I'd do another
one today will be beef and cheese me
tacos cuz you can't you can't go wrong
with a taco though you're like me about
Mexican people am I right now you may
wonder why this banana here is here
Sam you're a special reason I mean it
it's just yellow like Bob and my
favorite guest comes on the ground and
not because I'm gonna shut up my ass or
anything so let's look at the mini
conquer shall we oh oh my God mmm
let's take a buyout that tastes like
talk about I need something to
do washes debt that is like Taco Bell
it what what is in this that is
like dad looks like my PO
no I'm dead looks like my food doesn't
taste like my PO